(RAIN TRICKLING)
("ALL THE THINGS SHE
SAID" BY T.A.T.U.)
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID,
ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD,
RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD ♪
♪ RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID,
ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD,
RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID
ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ THIS IS NOT ENOUGH ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I'M IN SERIOUS SH,
I FEEL TOTALLY LOST ♪
♪ IF I'M ASKING FOR
HELP IT'S ONLY BECAUSE ♪
♪ BEING WITH YOU
HAS OPENED MY EYES ♪
♪ COULD I EVER BELIEVE
SUCH A PERFECT SURPRISE ♪
♪ I KEEP ASKING MYSELF,
WONDERING HOW ♪
♪ I KEEP CLOSING MY EYES
BUT I CAN'T BLOCK YOU OUT ♪
♪ WANNA FLY TO A PLACE
WHERE IT'S JUST YOU AND ME ♪
♪ NOBODY ELSE, SO
WE CAN BE FREE ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID,
ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD,
RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD ♪
♪ RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID,
ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD,
RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ THIS IS NOT ENOUGH ♪
♪ YA SOSHLA S'UMA, -MA ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID,
ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ AND I'M ALL MIXED UP,
FEELING CORNERED AND RUSHED ♪
♪ THEY SAY IT'S MY FAULT
BUT I WANT HER SO MUCH ♪
♪ WANNA FLY HER AWAY WHERE
THE SUN AND THE RAIN ♪
♪ COME IN OVER MY FACE,
WASH AWAY ALL THE SHAME ♪
♪ WHEN THEY STOP AND
STARE, DON'T WORRY ME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M FEELING FOR HER
WHAT SHE'S FEELING FOR ME ♪
♪ I CAN TRY TO PRETEND,
I CAN TRY TO FORGET ♪
♪ BUT IT'S DRIVING ME MAD,
GOING OUT OF MY HEAD ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID,
ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD,
RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD ♪
♪ RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID,
ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD,
RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ THIS IS NOT ENOUGH ♪
♪ YA SOSHLA S'UMA, -MA ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID,
ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS
SHE SAID, SHE SAID ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID,
ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ MOTHER LOOKING AT ME ♪
♪ TELL ME, WHAT DO YOU SEE ♪
♪ YES, I'VE LOST MY MIND ♪
♪ DADDY LOOKING AT ME ♪
♪ WILL I EVER BE FREE ♪
♪ HAVE I CROSSED THE LINE ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID,
ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD,
RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD ♪
♪ RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID,
ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD,
RUNNING THROUGH MY HEAD ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
♪ THIS IS NOT ENOUGH ♪
♪ YA SOSHLA S'UMA, -MA ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID,
ALL THE THINGS SHE SAID ♪
(RAIN TRICKLING)
(LAMP CREAKING)